#questions Created by me and some sourced from quizbreaker.com
data = [
    {
        #Question 1
        "question": "What is the Capital City of United States of America?", 
        "answer": 4,
        "option1": "Los Angeles",
        "option2": "Las Vegas",
        "option3": "New York",
        "option4": "Washington DC",
    },
    {
        #Question 2
        "question": "How many are in a bakers dozen?",
        "answer": 3,
        "option1": "12",
        "option2": "11",
        "option3": "13",
        "option4": "24",
    },
    {
        #Question 3
        "question": "What is the biggest Country in the World?",
        "answer": 2,
        "option1": "China",
        "option2": "Russia",
        "option3": "United States of America",
        "option4": "Australia",
    },
    {
        #Question 4
        "question": "What year was the moon landing?",
        "answer": 4,
        "option1": "1968",
        "option2": "120 BC",
        "option3": "2001",
        "option4": "1969",
    },
    {
        #Question 5
        "question": "How much robux does 60,000 credits in phantom forces cost?",
        "answer": 1,
        "option1": "5,000",
        "option2": "25,000",
        "option3": "60,000",
        "option4": "1,000",
    },
    {
        #Question 6
        "question": "How many CMs are in Inches?",
        "answer": 3,
        "option1": "2.62",
        "option2": "3.53",
        "option3": "2.54",
        "option4": "5.22",
    },
    {
        #Question 7
        "question": "What phobia is cynophobia?",
        "answer": 1,
        "option1": "Fear of Dogs",
        "option2": "Fear of Gum",
        "option3": "Fear of Cups",
        "option4": "Fear of Smoke",
    },
    {
        #Question 8
        "question": "What is the flower, on the national flag of India?",
        "answer": 3,
        "option1": "Rose",
        "option2": "Lavender",
        "option3": "Lotus",
        "option4": "Daisy",
    },
    {
        #Question 9
        "question": "Who named the Pacific Ocean?",
        "answer": 2,
        "option1": "Lionel Messi",
        "option2": "Ferdinand Magellan",
        "option3": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "option4": "Olajide Olayinka Williams Olatunji",
    },
    {
        #Question 10
        "question": "Who was the first women to recieve a Nobel Prize?",
        "answer": 4,
        "option1": "Kate Sheppard",
        "option2": "Bill Nye",
        "option3": "Rosalind Franklin",
        "option4": "Marie Curie",
    },
    {
        #Question 11
        "question": "What is the rarest M&M color?",
        "answer": 1,
        "option1": "Brown",
        "option2": "Black",
        "option3": "White",
        "option4": "Teal",
    },
    {
        #Question 12
        "question": "What is the loudest animal on Earth?",
        "answer": 1,
        "option1": "Sperm Whale",
        "option2": "Polar Bear",
        "option3": "Humpback Whale",
        "option4": "Howler Monkeys",
    },
    {
        #Question 13
        "question": "The unicorn is the national animal of which country?",
        "answer": 3,
        "option1": "Ireland",
        "option2": "Greenland",
        "option3": "Scotland",
        "option4": "Norway",
    },
    {
        #Question 14
        "question": "A group of ravens are known as?",
        "answer": 1,
        "option1": "Unkindness",
        "option2": "Murder",
        "option3": "Bully",
        "option4": "Depreach",
    },
    {
        #Question 15
        "question": "What type of animal is the Flemish Giant?",
        "answer": 4,
        "option1": "Sea Lion",
        "option2": "Elephant",
        "option3": "Hippopotamus",
        "option4": "Rabbit",
    },
    {
        #Question 16
        "question": "How long is New Zealands 90 Mile Beach?",
        "answer": 2,
        "option1": "90 Miles",
        "option2": "55 Miles",
        "option3": "60 Miles",
        "option4": "45 Miles",
    },
    {
        #Question 17
        "question": "What is measured in Mickeys?",
        "answer": 1,
        "option1": "The speed of a computer mouse",
        "option2": "The amount of food sold on a daily at Mcdonalds",
        "option3": "The amount of frames in a disney movie",
        "option4": "The amount of customers at disney land a year",
    },
    {
        #Question 18
        "question": "What is a duel between 3 people called?",
        "answer": 4,
        "option1": "Truet",
        "option2": "Tripete",
        "option3": "Tripular",
        "option4": "Truel",
    },
    {
        #Question 19
        "question": "How many countries are in Africa?",
        "answer": 3,
        "option1": "55",
        "option2": "59",
        "option3": "54",
        "option4": "56",
    },
    {
        #Question 20
        "question": "Where was Hawaiian Pizza made?",
        "answer": 2,
        "option1": "USA",
        "option2": "Canada",
        "option3": "Spain",
        "option4": "Italy",
    },
]